grabagun.com 2011-12-31

# Grabagun.com Customer Service Online Gun Store

Grabagun.com respects your privacy and is committed to protecting it. Grabagun.com provides this Privacy Statement to inform you of our Privacy Policy and how that information is used.

Grabagun.com will not sell, rent or lease your personal information to others. Grabagun.com will not share your personal information with third parties.

This Privacy Statement applies only to the Grabagun.com owned website and domain.

The Grabagun.com web site occasionally provides links to third-party websites for your education or convenience. If you access those links, you will leave the Grabagun.com site and domain. Grabagun.com does not control those sites or their privacy practices, which may differ from Grabagun.com. We do not endorse or make any representations about third-party Web sites. The Grabagun.com Privacy Statement does not cover the personal data you choose to give to unrelated third party Web sites. We encourage you to review the privacy policy of any company before submitting your personal information.

Grabagun.com is committed to protecting the information you provide us. To prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, to maintain data accuracy, and to ensure the appropriate use of the information, Grabagun.com has in place appropriate security procedures to safeguard the information we collect.

We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption when collecting or transferring sensitive data such as credit card information. SSL encryption is designed to make the information unreadable by anyone but us. This security measure is working when you see either the symbol of an unbroken key or closed lock (depending on your browser) on the bottom of your browser window.

Credit card numbers are used only for processing payment and kept secure and confidential.

If there are updates to the terms of the Grabagun.com Online Privacy Statement, we will post those changes and update the revision date in this document, so you will always know what information we collect online, how we use it, and what choices you have.

We value your opinions. If you have comments or questions about our privacy policy, please contact us at customerservice@grabagun.com.
